Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design, Corcoran School of Art + Design records, circa 1908-2012 COR0009.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Dean's records, 1968-2003; Series 11
  - Samuel Hoi records, 1989-2000; Series 11 subseries 6
    - Financial Aid Survey, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 62, Folder 48)
    - FTE, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 62, Folder 49)
    - Seven Small Schools Summary Data, 1984-1985; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 62, Folder 50)
    - Postsecondary Student Outcomes A Feasibility, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 62, Folder 51)
    - School Benefit Roy Litchenstein: Past, Present, and Future, 1994 June 7; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 62, Folder 52)
    - "In the Presence of Matisse" School Benefit, 1993 March 5; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 62, Folder 53)
    - Special Events, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 62, Folder 54)
    - Special Events - Board Room, etc. Info RE: Caterers, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 62, Folder 55)
    - Librarian - Job Description Job Announcement, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Librarian Search, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - 97 Director of Admissions Search, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Enrollment Management job description, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - International Visitors Biographical Information, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Miscellanous Resumes, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Job Descriptions - School Staff, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Inquiries - Faculty Positions, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Board of Trustees/ Executive Committee, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, 1995; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - The Corcoran Gallery of Art Annual Review Museum and School Operations, 1993; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Executive Committee Meetings, 1993; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Meeting of the Executive Committee, 1992 October 19; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Meeting of the Executive Committee, 1992 June 22; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Meeting of the Executive Committee, 1992 April 13; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Meeting of the Executive Committee, 1992 February 10; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Meeting of the Executive Committee, 1991 December 16; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Meeting of the Executive Committee, 1991 October 21; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Meeting of the Executive Committee, 1991 August 5; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Meeting of the Executive Committee, 1991 June 17; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Meeting of the Executive Committee, 1991 February 25; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1991 January 28; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Meeting of the Board of Overseers, 1992 April 29; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Meeting of the Board of Overseers, 1992 March 11; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Meeting of the Board of Overseers, 1992 January 22; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Meeting of the Board of Overseers, 1991 November 25; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Building & Ground Committee Meetings, 1992-1993; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Samuel C. Hoi Building & Grounds Committee Minutes of meeting, 1991 September 26; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Meetings of the Policy and Planning Committee of the Board of Trustees, 1993; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Faculty Teaching Schedules, 1995; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - Faculty Exhibition National Academy of Sciences, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 31)
    - Faculty Shows, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 32)
    - Chairs Council Meeting Minutes, 1996-1997; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 33)
    - Chairs Council Correspondence/Memos, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 34)
    - Department Chairs, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 35)
    - Chairs Council Meeting, 1988 October 4; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 36)
    - AAUP Corcoran Chapter, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 37)
    - Faculty Association, 1996-1997; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 38)
    - Operations Review, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 39)
    - Faculty Association, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 40)
    - Faculty Association By-Laws, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 41)
    - Faculty Birthdays, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 42)
    - Affrimative Action Policy Draft Copies from Fac. Association, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 43)
    - Faculty Development Fund, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 44)
    - Faculty Development, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 45)
    - Technical Assistants Salary, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 46)
    - Hiring Policy, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 47)
    - Retirement Faculty, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 48)
    - Faculty Evaulation, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 49)
    - Faculty Promotion History, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 50)
    - Sabbatical, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 51)
    - Sabbatical Points, 1998-1999; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 52)
    - Sabbatical Points, 1996-1997; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 53)
    - Sabbatical Points, 1997; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 54)
    - Faculty Promotions, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 55)
    - Faculty Promotion & Sabbatical, 1997-1998; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 56)
    - Faculty Promotions, 1996-1997; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 57)
    - Faculty Promotions, 1995-1996; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 58)
    - Faculty Promotions, 1994-1995; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 59)
    - Faculty Promotions, 1993-1994; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 63, Folder 60)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1992 September 39; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1992 April 29; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1992 March 11; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1992 January 22; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1991 November 25; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1991 September 23; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Board of Overseers Meeting Corcoran School of Art, 1991 April 29; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1991 April 29; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1991 January 23; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1990 December 7; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1990 November 26; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Art School Committee Meeting, 1990 September 19; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Board of Trustees Committees, 1996-1997; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees of the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1996; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Board Retreat Summary, 1995; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Corcoran Gallery of Art Board of Trustees Retreat, 1995; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1995; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1995 May 22; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1995 January 30; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - A Meeting of the Board of Trustees of the Corcoran Gallery of Art, 1994 November 29; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Board of Trustees Retreat The Aspen Institute, 1994 October 14-16; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - A Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1993 September 26; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1994 May 23; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1994 March 28; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Minutes of the Meeting of the Exhibitions Committee of the Museum Board of Overseers, 1994 March 3; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Planning for the Board of Trustees Retreat, 1994; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1994 January 24; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Meeting of the Museum Board of Overseers, 1993 November 15; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Board of Trustees Meeting, 1993 November 22; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Minutes of the Meeting of the Museum Board of Overseers, 1994 October 12; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Museum Board of Overseers, 1993 November; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1993 September 29; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1991 September 16; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Meeting of the Museum Board of Overseers, 1993 June 9; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Meeting of the Museum Board of Overseers, 1993 April 13; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Preliminary Report on School for Meeting of the Board of Trustees, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - School Report, 1992 September 14; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - Special "Blue Ribbon" Committee of the Board of Trustees, 1989 Fall; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 38)
    - By-Laws Charter, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 39)
    - Finance Committee Meeting, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 40)
    - Governance, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 41)
    - Minutes All Staff Meeting, 1989 September 15; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 42)
    - Prospective Board Members, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 43)
    - Merritt C. Ludwig, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 44)
    - Trustee Resume, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 45)
    - Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1993 May 10; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 46)
    - Meeting of the Board of Directors, 1993 April 12; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 47)
    - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1992 November 16; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 48)
    - Annual Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1992 May 4; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 49)
    - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1992 March 16; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 50)
    - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1992 January 13; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 51)
    - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1991 November 18; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 52)
    - Meeting of the Board of Trustees, 1992 September 14; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 53)
    - Special Meeting, 1992 September 14; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 64, Folder 54)
    - Memos, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Memoradum, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Memos to Faculty, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Student Letters, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence file: A, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Correspondence file: B, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence file: C, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - Correspondence file: D, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Correspondence file: E, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Correspondence file: F, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Correspondence file: G, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - Correspondence file: H, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence file: I, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Correspondence file: J, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence file: K, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence file: L, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Correspondence file: Mc, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Correspondence file: M, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence file: N, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence file: O, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Correspondence file: P, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Correspondence file: Q, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Correspondence file: R, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Correspondence file: S, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Faculty Promotions, 1992-1993; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Annual Plus Not on TIAA/CREF, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Student-Faculty Ratio Data, 1996; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Sabbatical Leave Point System, 1994 September; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Corcoran Full-time Faculty Teaching History Survey, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Sabbatical Points Survey, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Swain School of Design Full-time Faculty Personnel Policy Manual, 1985; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Who to ask regarding..., circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Faculty Manual Draft the Corcoran School of Art, 1989 October 13; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Grievance Procedures, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Faculty Manual, 1986; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - The Changing Workplace, 1994; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Memorandum to the Art School Committee concerning the general situation and the activities of the faculty, 1984 May 21; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - CSA Faculty Manual/ Proposal for Grivenances, 1990; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - CSA Faculty Manual/Information for Faculty, 1992; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - CSA Faculty Manual/Information for Faculty, 1993; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - CSA Faculty Manual/Information for Faculty, 1994; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Faculty Manual, 1982; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Employment Information/Tips/Readings, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Higher Education Executive Associates Inc. Faculty Handbook Seminar, 1990; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Memphis College of Art Faculty Handbook, 1988; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Minneapolis College of Art & Design, 1990; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Oregon Art Institute/Pacific Northwest College of Art Faculty Handbook, 1990-1991; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - San Francisco Art Institute Faculty Manual & Personnel Policy Statement, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - On Sammy's Calendar, 1996; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Staff Meetings, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Chairs Council, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - Museum School Collaboration, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - Administrative Mentor Program Susan's, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - Studio 405 OD/CE Catalog Production, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - Academic Calendar, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Old Faculty Lists, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Address list & phone numbers, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - AAA Travel Agency: Travel Arranger Handbook, 1994; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Course Evaluations - Background, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - New Curriculum, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - CSA Courses/Labs Information (Schedules/Evaluations/Faculty), 1988-1996; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Swain Report, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Academic Studies Dept. Syllabi, 1995; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Academic Studies, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - ESL English as a Second Language, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 41)
    - Elderhostel, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 66, Folder 42)
    - Correspondence file: T, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence file: U, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Correspondence file: V, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Correspondence file: W, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence file: X-Y-Z, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Annmarie Garden Calvery County, Maryland, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Artwork, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Advertising Schedules, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - City Paper, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Washington Post, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Kids & Teen, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Washington Times, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Open Program Advertising, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - OP/CE Catalog, 1996 Summer; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Cadmus Magazines, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Open Program Info, 1995-1996; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Parent & Child magazine, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Washington Parent, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Families Newspaper, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Flyers, Brochure, Etc., circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Free Publicity Arts Events Calendars, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Public Service Announcements, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - WETA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - WLTT/94.7 FM, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Program Curriculm Outcomes (Rona's Subcommittee), circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 67, Folder 26)
    - Ceramic Course, 1996 Spring; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Architectural Workshop Evaluations I, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Computer Graphics Curriculum, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Computer Lab, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Computer Graphics (OP), circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Computer Graphics BFA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Interior Design, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Landscape Design, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - OP Paint/Draw, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Fine Arts Department, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Class Syllabi William Willis, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Fine Arts Retreat, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - The Foundations Program, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Design, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Fine Arts Electives, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - Drawing, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - Foundations, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - IRMA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - Graphic Design (Faculty, Studentst, General Information, Misc.), circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - Graphic Design BFA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Graphic Design (O.P.), circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Photography BFA, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Photography (O.P.), circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Printmaking, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Sculpture, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Open Sculpture Competition, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Summer- Ceramics Devers, 1991; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Courses Information, 1988-1994; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - I.R.M.A, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - Drawing, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - Design, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - Courses Information (Foundations Dept, IRMA, Fine Arts Elective), 1989-1990; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - Academic Studies Syllabi, 1989 Fall; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - Curriculum, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - Graphic Design, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - Hubert Leckie Scholarship, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - Graphic Design Courses, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - Photo - Curriculum, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - Children's Workshop, circa 1990s; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 68, Folder 39)
    - College Board of Overseers, 2000 May 1; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - College Board of Overseers, 2000 February 14; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - College Board of Overseers, 1999 November 17; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - College Board of Overseers, 1999 September 22; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - School Board of Overseers, 1999 April 28; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - School Board of Overseers, 1999 February 17; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - School Board of Overseers, 1998 November 18; Series 11 subseries 6 (Box 69, Folder 7)